Hello.
こんにちは
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I am doing.
してます
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないでください
It's cute.
可愛いですね
Your skin is so white.
肌白いね、めっちゃ
Can I ask you a few questions?
ちょっといろいろ質問してもいいですか?
What do you usually do now?
今は何してるの、普段?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
What year are you in?
何年生なの?
1st year student.
1年生
How old are they both now?
両方は今、いくつ?
I'm 18 years old.
18歳です
You're young.
若いね
I just started school.
入学したばっかりなんだ
fun?
楽しい?
It's fun.
楽しいです
Great, that's the problem.
すごいね、問題なんだ
What are you playing, an instrument?
何やってるの、楽器?
I play the piano.
ピアノやってます
Oh, it's a piano.
あ、ピアノなんだ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Have you been doing this since you were a child?
子供の頃からやってるの?
Yes, fine.
はい、結構
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
Do you have any dreams for the future?
何か将来の夢とかあるの?
I want to be a music teacher in the future.
将来は音楽の先生になりたいなって
Ah, that's nice.
あ、いいですね
Where, school, elementary school, etc.
どこ、学校、小学校とか
primary school.
小学校
That seems like something.
なんかいそうだよね
Like a beautiful teacher.
美人教師みたいな
Thank you.
ありがとうね
nice.
いいね
Are you working part-time now?
今、バイトやってたりしちゃうの?
I'm working part-time.
バイトやってます
What are you doing?
何やってるの?
I had a part-time job at an ivy shop.
ツタ屋でバイトした
Ivy shop?
ツタ屋?
Why Tsutaya?
なんでツタ屋の?
why?
なんで?
I can't really say anything.
特に言えないです
especially.
特に
By the way, don't you do piano work as a part-time job?
なんか、ピアノのそれ仕事とかは バイト目でしてない?
I don't play the piano, but I teach piano to small children.
ピアノはしてないんですけど、 ちっちゃい子とかに ピアノ教え
Thank you.
た り
That's right.
そうなんだ
That's about it.
それぐらいね
You're good at it, aren't you?
上手なんだね
Don't you like little kids?
ちっちゃい子は好きじゃない?
child.
子供
I also like children.
子供も好きです
Do you like children too?
子供も好き?
I also like children.
子供も好き
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるの?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏いないんです
Are you not there?
いないの?
There aren't that many boys at my school.
学校はあれか、なんか あんまり男子とかいないんです
It seems like it's all girls.
女子ばっかりみたいな
that's right.
そう です
What about the encounter?
出会いがじゃあ?
I haven't had any encounters.
出会いもないですね
Have you ever had a boyfriend like that?
今まで、そういう彼氏行ったことはある?
Only one boyfriend.
彼氏、一人だけ
Oh, just one person?
あ、一人だけ?
When I was in high school.
高校の時に
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
We're separated.
分かれちゃったな
I understand.
分かりましたね
Why did we split up?
なんで分かれちゃったの?
We went to different universities and didn't have time to meet up.
ちょっと大学が別々になって、 会う時間もなくて
I see.
そっか
Understood.
分かりました
Did you have sex with that boyfriend?
その彼氏とはさ、 エッチなことしてた?
I did.
しました
first time.
初めて
first time?
初めて?
yes.
はい
fault.
あら
how was it?
どうだった?
it was good.
良かった
it was good?
良かった?
how was it?
どうだった?
it was good.
良かった
how was it?
どうだった?
The nails were done beautifully.
素敵なネイルを奏でられた
nice nails.
素敵なネイル
Didn't it hurt the first time?
初めて痛かったりしてなかったの?
It hurt at first.
最初は痛かったです
Was it painful at first?
最 初は痛かった?
But I guess I'm used to it, I guess I'm used to it.
けど、慣れたな、慣れたなみたいな
Okay, so you've done it a few times?
結構じゃあ何回かやってたの?
I agree.
そうですね
It was long.
長かったんで
The time we were dating.
付 き合ってた時間が
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ってたの?
About 2 years.
2年くらい
long?
長く?
long.
長い
It's a very intentional map.
めっちゃ意地図なんだね
It's an intentional map.
意地図なんですね
It was a plan, but unfortunately it was divided.
意地図だけど、ちょっと残念なことに分かれちゃった
That's right.
そうなんだ
Well, I haven't been doing that kind of thing lately.
ちょっとじゃあ、最近はじゃあ、そういうことしてないっていう
What are you doing?
何してる?
It's been a while, it's been a while.
ちょっとじゃあ、久々の
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないで
Next time, there's a lot of things.
次はいろいろね、ちょっと
I'll do it.
やっちゃいます
Your face doesn't look good.
顔落ちんね
I said that my face fell off.
顔落ちって言っちゃいました
It's white.
白いね
no.
いや
It's white.
白いです
You're not tanned at all, are you?
全然、日に焼けてないでしょ?
I'm applying daily medicine to my eyes.
日薬の目塗ってるんで
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Yeah, what?
そう、何?
No, what do you do on your day off?
いや、休みの日とか何してるの?
Day off.
休みの日
I already have a part-time job.
もうバイトです
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
I'm sweating a little.
ちょっと汗かいてる
汗かいてるよ、ちょっと
It's a little hot.
ちょっと暑いです
hot?
暑い?
I'm nervous.
緊張しちゃって
Are you playing the piano with your fingers?
指でピアノ弾いてるの?
that's right.
そうです
nice
素敵な
That's a nice finger.
素敵な指だね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だもんね
is that so.
そうですか
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Do you do this?
こういうことするの?
Long time no see.
久々
It's been a while.
久々です
Since high school.
高校以来
that's right.
そうです
Wow, it's black.
すごい、黒なんだね
yes.
はい
Because it's white.
白いから
I thought it was white.
白なのかと思ったら
This looks like a piano.
これはピアノみたいになってるね
I agree.
そうですね
what happened?
どうしたの?
I hid it.
隠した
You hid it.
隠しましたね
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいです
lie?
嘘?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
picture?
え?
yes?
そう?
Don't be difficult
難しくないで
Sho?
しょ?
scared.
怖 い
amazing.
すごい
It's cute though.
可愛いんだけど
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
yes?
そう?
I'm wearing it more and more, but I'm taking it off.
どんどん着てるけど、脱がしてるよ
It's beautiful, nose.
綺麗だね、鼻
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
My body temperature is getting hot.
体温かくなって
That's a really embarrassing thing to do.
めっちゃ恥ずかしいやってるじゃん
Let's see if it's naughty.
エッチなのチューするね
Would you like to see something so naughty?
そんなエッチなのチューする?
It's reflected.
映ってるよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
cute.
可愛い
Do you want to take it off?
脱ぎたいの?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
cute.
可愛い
You have a nice butt.
良いお尻してるね
Stick your butt out.
尻突き出して
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
It's so sexy.
すごいセクシーだよ
You have a beautiful body.
綺麗な体してるね
You have a really beautiful body.
すごい綺麗な体してるね
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
めっちゃ綺麗だね
Look!
見てほら
It's really strong.
すごい強いね
It's getting better though.
なっちゃいますけど
Have you ever been licked by Kin-chan?
キンちゃんに舐めたことある?
It's really good.
すごいうまいね
That's amazing.
すごいね
There is a feeling of suction.
吸い付き感が
That's amazing.
すごいね
Why such a chance?
なんでそんなチャンスなんの?
amazing.
すごい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels really good though.
めっちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
why?
なんで?